<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
	xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss"
	xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Books Archive &bull; Mixed Bag</title>
	<atom:link href="/book/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/book/</link>
	<description>For All your Fiction and Miscellaneous Reading Needs</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 12:37:54 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.1</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://i0.wp.com/www.hemas-mixedbag.com/wp-content/uploads/2016/05/money-bag-2-256x256.png?fit=32%2C32</url>
	<title>Books Archive &bull; Mixed Bag</title>
	<link>/book/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">111981179</site>	<item>
		<title>Raising Your Voice &#8211; An Anthology by Women Writers</title>
		<link>/book/raising-voice-anthology-women-writers/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mixedbag]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2018 02:50:37 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=mbdb_book#038;p=2576</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>"Raising Your Voice" is an anthology of essays, poetry and short fiction, all written by women. I'm proud to be one of them. This is the annual anthology published by The Same - a trailblazing literary magazine for women.</p>
<p>My inclusion in this book is especially exciting because my story - "Finding Saraswati" was placed third in their short story competition. Finding Saraswati is about a new bride who moves from a small town in South India to Delhi in the turbulent 1940s. With this political scene in the background, she has to navigate her life in a new place, with a new husband and speaking a new language. How does she cope? And does she eventually find herself?</p>
<p>I hope you enjoy this story. I'm thrilled to share this space with 21 powerful women with their thought-provoking writing.</p>
<p>To buy this anthology, click here.</p>
<p>And if do read it, please consider leaving us a review on the Amazon page. Happy Reading!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/book/raising-voice-anthology-women-writers/">Raising Your Voice &#8211; An Anthology by Women Writers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Mixed Bag</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2576</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Sensorially Challenged &#8211; Volume 1</title>
		<link>/book/sensorially-challenged/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mixedbag]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2018 14:04:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=mbdb_book#038;p=2494</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>&#160;</p>
<p>I'm not superstitious, but December is proving to be a good month for my writing. This day, last year I was "discovered" by WordPress Discover. What a heady feeling that was. I remember waking up to a million notifications and comments.</p>
<p>And this year, I'm elated to be included in a flash fiction anthology called "Sensorially Challenged", alongside 99 other talented authors. These short-stories include references to all five senses. They're spicy, aromatic, gorgeous, silky, and dulcet. Cough, *gift idea* cough.</p>
<p>Profits from this book go to The National Literacy Trust, a charity that gives disadvantaged children the literacy skills they need to succeed in life by helping to improve reading, writing, speaking and listening skills in the UK’s poorest communities.</p>
<p>The book is now available on Amazon - go get it now !!</p>
<p>I hope you enjoy reading these little sensory treats! Happy New Year!</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/book/sensorially-challenged/">Sensorially Challenged &#8211; Volume 1</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Mixed Bag</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2494</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chicken Soup for the Soul &#8211; My Kind (of) America</title>
		<link>/book/chicken-soup-soul/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mixedbag]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 00:24:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=mbdb_book#038;p=2340</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Three years ago, if someone had told me I would be a writer someday, I would have laughed out loud. But life has a way of putting us in unexpected situations, while it sits back, popcorn in hand to see what we do in those situations. I quit my day job four years back to become a SAHM. Blogging helped maintain my sanity in those crazy, sleep deprived months which every new parent goes through.</p>
<p>I didn't know what to write about then. I tried my voice with everything I could think of - parenting, recipes, fashion(shudder!). My blog was truly a "Mixed Bag". Then one day, yes it was exactly that, one day, I stumbled across this wonderful writing group which gave me direction, the voice I was looking for. If you're a writer and  haven't checked out YeahWrite, please remedy the situation immediately.</p>
<p>I immersed myself into writing fiction, it was such a delicious escape from the real world! It still is. But on rare occasions, I write personal essays. When I first came to America, I volunteered as a literacy tutor at the local library. Many years later, I wrote about it. I submitted it to "Chicken Soup for the Soul" on a whim. It was an uplifting story, maybe they would like it. I submitted it and promptly forgot about it.</p>
<p>Imagine my surprise six months later, when I got an email from one of the editors at Chicken Soup with news that I had made it to the final round of edits to their anthology titled "My Kind America"! I worked with the editors on some minor edits and finally, tomorrow is the day when "Chicken Soup for the Soul - My Kind (of) America" hits stores.</p>
<p>Yours truly is at #91!</p>
<p>It is such a dream come true. This is why you should submit your writing, you never know who might read it and like it!</p>
<p>&#160;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/book/chicken-soup-soul/">Chicken Soup for the Soul &#8211; My Kind (of) America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Mixed Bag</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">2340</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ellipsis: An Anthology of Humorous Short Stories</title>
		<link>/book/ellipsis-anthology-humorous-short-stories/</link>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[mixedbag]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 15:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">/?post_type=mbdb_book#038;p=1506</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Please join me as I celebrate being published for the very first time. One of my fiction pieces has been published as part of an anthology of short humorous stories. I'm featured with 16 very talented authors.</p>
<p>'Ellipsis' is part sarcasm, part satire and a whole lot of laughter. And the best part is, all the money we get from the sale of Ellipsis goes to charity.<br />
♦♦♦♦♦<br />
Do you need a laugh? Hey, we all do! This collection will take you from reality to fantasy, from cute to profane, and from grins to guffaws. These seventeen original stories are packed with sarcasm, satire, and wickedness, and are so completely tongue in cheek there’s no way you can avoid a smile.</p>
<p>Authors hailing from faraway places on either side of the Atlantic Ocean, in big cities and out in the countryside, offer their insights into what we call humor. Comedy is hard work. Humor is so often experienced in a particular situation and is often impossible to reproduce. Writing funny stories must come from conditions which allow the writer to laugh at himself. If we could remember all the funny things that happen during a day (or night), we would laugh a whole lot more.</p>
<p>This anthology was collected with giving in mind. All comedians live to be laughed at. Giving your laughter nourishes their souls. And all the money received from sales of Ellipsis will go to charity.</p>
<p>Humor and humanity—after all, that’s what life’s all about.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/book/ellipsis-anthology-humorous-short-stories/">Ellipsis: An Anthology of Humorous Short Stories</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">Mixed Bag</a>.</p>
]]></description>
		
		
		
		<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">1506</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/

Object Caching 29/140 objects using memcached
Page Caching using memcached 
Lazy Loading (feed)
Minified using disk
Database Caching 3/19 queries in 0.008 seconds using disk

Served from: www.hemas-mixedbag.com @ 2023-05-19 22:58:02 by W3 Total Cache
-->